#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/jun-nguyen-819163149 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Graphic Design Management Teamwork

### Certifications

3D Design

Mobile User Experience (UX) Design

# Jun Nguyen

**UI/UX** Designer

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

## Summary

I'm Jun, a Vietnam born digital designer currently looking for opportunities in UI/UX job. Over the 4years of my career, my portfolio includes user interface design, brand & identity design, illustration, and photography. While at Central Group the last year, I've worked on printing and social media artwork for a range of international retailers (Mark&Spencer,F&F, Lee Jeans), in the major of fashion.

Since leaving Central Group, I've gained a wealth of both freelance and agency experience. Now, I'm mainly working with startups as a freelancer, includes Jen Trading, Yoonek Studio, Jennie Beauty.

If you think I'd be a good fit for your team, please get in touch and we can chat.

## Experience

PlusNsoft UI/UX Designer February 2020 - Present (5 years 2 months) Vietnam

Central Group
Graphic Designer
February 2018 - February 2019 (1 year 1 month)

## Education

Truòng Dai hoc Dan Lap Van Lang
(2015 - 2018)